<language>
	<island>
		<apollo>
			<text1>How may I inspire you today?</text1>
			<text2>Never mind.</text2>
			<text3>Farewell.</text3>
			<text4>Can you teach me a song to play on my pipe?</text4>
			<text5>Sorry, I can't help you.</text5>
			<text6>You must first prove yourself a worthy musician. Play what I play...</text6>
			<text7>You are not yet worthy. Try again.</text7>
			<text8>You are a worthy musician. Listen and remember. Play this tune for Cerberus and he will fall asleep.</text8>
			<text9>I'm not sure yet. I'll get back to you.</text9>
		</apollo>
		
		<cerberus>
			<text1>I'm not strong enough to do this, but somebody else might be.</text1>
			<text2>I need to be closer to the beast.</text2>
			<text3>A little pebble like this is no match for Herc's mighty muscles!</text3>
			<text4>Go on ahead. I'll be waiting out here.</text4>
		</cerberus>
		
		<grove>
			<text1>The gods like to receive offerings.</text1>
			<text2>Can you help me clean this graffiti? I'll pay you one drachma.</text2>
			<text3>Thanks for your help! May Hades look favorably upon you.</text3>
			<text4>So terrible! I heard Zeus himself is responsible for this graffiti!</text4>
			<text5>You must be on an errand from the gods to pass this point.</text5>
			<text6>To appease a god, you must leave an appropriate offering upon their altar.</text6>
		</grove>
		
		<hadesPit1>
			<text1>No door handle...It must open from the other side.</text1>
			<text2>It seems harmless enough.</text2>
		</hadesPit1>
		
		<hadesPit2>
			<text1>I am Charon, ferryman of the underworld.</text1>
			<text2>Can I cross this, uh, river?</text2>
			<text3>I will ferry you across the divide, but it is a dangerous journey.</text3>
			<text4>I'm ready. Let's go.</text4>
			<text5>As you wish...</text5>
		</hadesPit2>
		
		<hadesThrone>
			<text1>You must be Hades.</text1>
			<text2>I know why you have come. My brother Zeus is very dangerous.</text2>
			<text3>I can't leave the Underworld. But I will give you my crown.</text3>
			<text4>Thank you, young hero. You have restored the balance of power.</text4>
		</hadesThrone>
		
		<hercsHut>
			<text1>Autographed Photos Only 10 Drachmas!</text1>
			<text2>Excuse me.</text2>
			<text3>Do you want an autograph?</text3>
			<text4>Your sister Athena said you could help me.</text4>
			<text5>Sure. I'll cut you a deal. Only nine drachmas for an autograph.</text5>
			<text6>I don't need an autograph. I need your help. I'm on a mission from Zeus.</text6>
			<text7>Sorry, kid. I need a better reason than that to leave this comfy spot.</text7>
			<text8>Please help me!</text8>
			<text9>You again?</text9>
			<text10>You have to help me. Your father wants to rule all of Poptropica.</text10>
			<text11>Tempting. But I really don't feel like walking right now.</text11>
			<text12>If I can find a way to transport us, will you come?</text12>
			<text13>Sure, whatever.</text13>
			<text14>You don't have to. Aphrodite gave me a mirror. We can teleport where we need to go.</text14>
			<text15>Hmm. Autograph sales have been slow lately. Let's do it!</text15>
			<text16>OMZ! Did you hear? Zeus is like, soooo jealous of his brothers.</text16>
			<text17>LOL! That's probably because Poseidon has a better beard!</text17>
			<text18>The pomegranate punch is to die for!</text18>
			<text19>No thanks.</text19>
		</hercsHut>
		
		<hydra>
			<text1>The music has no effect on the Hydra!</text1>
		</hydra>
		
		<labyrinth>
			<text1>I was once known as Pan.</text1>
			<text2>Can you help me through the labyrinth?</text2>
			<text3>Remember this: There is more than one way to read the bones.</text3>
		</labyrinth>
		
		<labyrinthRoom>
			<text1>I am the Minotaur, and this is my labyrinth.</text1>
			<text2>Uh... can I please have the ring in your nose?</text2>
			<text3>I only grant favors to those who can find the way through my labyrinth.</text3>
			<text4>I completed the labyrinth!</text4>
			<text5>I can't believe you're still alive.</text5>
			<text6>So... can I have the ring now?</text6>
			<text7>It is yours.</text7>
			<text8>This ring is one of the sacred items I need to give to Zeus.</text8>
			<text9>Zeus can't be trusted. Be careful.</text9>
			<text10>Mortals get on my nerves. Go away or I just may eat you.</text10>
		</labyrinthRoom>
		
		<labyrinthSnake>
			<text1>A bit foggy this evening, isn't it?</text1>
			<text2>Indeed, Neptune himself has covered the sea with his gossamer cloak.</text2>
			<text3>Weird, I thought it was just water vapor?</text3>
			<text4>Aye, there be much you don't know, har har!</text4>
			<text5>Know any good poems?</text5>
			<text6>The moon shone pale as bone, as I stood there alone...</text6>
		</labyrinthSnake>
		
		<mainStreet>
			<text1>It's locked, and that's one hefty padlock!</text1>
			<text2>The gate is locked!</text2>
			<text3>May the gods watch over you, stranger.</text3>
			<text4>Hercules is signing autographs today!</text4>
			<text5>Hercules is my hero!</text5>
			<text6>You're my hero!</text6>
			<text7>Have you ever seen such a fine looking goat?</text7>
			<text8>Hey, aren't you the one who defeated Zeus?</text8>
			<text9>Clouds are forming. Zeus must be in a bad mood.</text9>
			<text10>Our hero has returned!</text10>
			<text11>After you...</text11>
			<text12>Locked to puny mortals like you, maybe. But not to the mighty Hercules!</text12>
			<text13>Watch and learn, grasshopper.</text13>
			<text14>Wow! I can see Mount Olympus from here!</text14>
			<text15>I saw the entire battle from here. Awesome!</text15>
		</mainStreet>
		
		<mountOlympus>
			<text1>Yikes! Is that what I think it is!?</text1>
			<text2>It's just a pesky snake. I'll take care of it.</text2>
			<text3>Medusa!? Uh oh, this is not good.</text3>
			<text4>Don't feel sorry for me. I got what I always wanted... a statue on Mount Olympus!</text4>
			<text5>You picked the wrong snake to mess with, buddy.</text5>
			<text6>Get your bags of wind here! Only one Drachma!</text6>
			<text7>Thank you. Here's your bag of wind!</text7>
			<text8>One refill, coming up!</text8>
		</mountOlympus>
		
		<mountOlympus2>
			<text1>What about Zeus?</text1>
			<text2>Not if I can help it!</text2>
			<text3>Foolish mortal! How dare you trespass in my realm!?</text3>
			<text4>Now you and my treacherous brothers will suffer my wrath!</text4>
			<text5>Well done. You saved Poptropica!</text5>
			<text6>He'll have to be satisfied with ruling the Heavens of Mythology Island for now.</text6>
			<text7>Please take this reward as a token of my gratitude.</text7>
		</mountOlympus2>
		
		<mountOlympus3>
			<text1>I give up! I give up!!! Take your items back. I promise I'll be good.</text1>
		</mountOlympus3>
			
		<olympusMuseum>
			<text1><![CDATA[Athena<br/>Zeus's daughter is as sharp as one of his thunderbolts, which is why she's known as the goddess of wisdom.]]></text1>
			<text2>She is also a warrior goddess. Olives, snakes, and spiders are all sacred to Athena.</text2>
			<text3><![CDATA[Hephaestus<br/>This skilled son of Zeus and Hera could star in his own home improvement show if he wanted to.]]></text3>
			<text4>He is the god of blacksmiths and other craftsmen. He can make armor that no arrow can pierce.</text4>
			<text5><![CDATA[Hades<br/>This deadly serious god rules the Underworld. He's the brother of Zeus and Poseidon and the pomegranate is his sacred fruit.]]></text5>
			<text6><![CDATA[Zeus<br/>Zeus defeated his brothers Poseidon and Hades to become King of the gods. Don't mess with Zeus!]]></text6>
			<text7><![CDATA[Poseidon<br/>Zeus's brother rules the seas, from the smallest plankton to the largest sea monster.]]></text7>
			<text8><![CDATA[Apollo<br/>The original rock star, this shining son of Zeus is god of the sun and music.]]></text8>
			<text9>His followers include the nine Muses, minor goddesses who lend creative inspiration to those who ask.</text9>
			<text10><![CDATA[Hestia<br/>Zeus's older sister is the goddess of hearth and home.]]></text10>
			<text11>When she was a kid, she never got in trouble for having a messy room. Oil and water are sacred to her.</text11>
			<text12><![CDATA[Demeter<br/>Thank Demeter every time you eat a sandwich! The goddess of grains and the harvest is Zeus's sister.]]></text12>
			<text13><![CDATA[Hera<br/>Queen of Olympus and guardian of women and children. Peacocks are sacred to Hera.]]></text13>
			<text14><![CDATA[Dionysus<br/>The god of wine, he often leads mortals astray.]]></text14>
			<text15><![CDATA[Hermes<br/>This son of Zeus is the messenger of the gods, thanks to the winged cap and sandals his dad gave him.]]></text15>
			<text16><![CDATA[Aphrodite<br/>This goddess of love and beauty sprang into life from the foam of the sea.]]></text16>
			<text17>The rose is sacred to Aphrodite—although whatever you do, don't compare her to a rose.</text17>
			<text18>Aphrodite thinks she's more beautiful than any flower on earth.</text18>
			<text19><![CDATA[Artemis<br/>Apollo's twin sister is more of a nature girl.]]></text19>
			<text20>She's the goddess of hunting and protector of young animals. She always carries a bow and arrow.</text20>
			<text21><![CDATA[Ares<br/>Tougher than a mixed martial arts fighter, this son of Zeus is the god of war.]]></text21>
			<text22>His battle cry alone can bring down warriors on the battlefield.</text22>
			<text23>Come, brothers, we must defeat the Titans!</text23>
			<text24>Aaaaaaaaaaa aaaaaaaaaah!</text24>
			<text25>I rule the Underworld!</text25>
			<text26>I rule the Seas!</text26>
			<text27>I rule the Heavens! All must bow before me!</text27>
			<text28>I will never bow to you, brother.</text28>
			<text29>Nor I.</text29>
			<text30>Perhaps not now... but one day.</text30>
		</olympusMuseum>
		
		<poseidonBeach>
			<text1>Hey, dude, sweet waves today.</text1>
			<text2>You must be the lifeguard.</text2>
			<text3>Stay away from that underwater cave, dude!</text3>
			<text4>Underwater cave?</text4>
			<text5>A totally gnarly monster lives there.</text5>
			<text6>Thanks for the advice.</text6>
			<text7>No prob. I'm Triton. My old man is the king of this place.</text7>
			<text8>It's a great day to soak up the sun!</text8>
			<text9>LOL! Poseidon would never let that happen!</text9>
			<text10>I heard that Zeus wants to rule the seas, too.</text10>
			<text11>Looks like you're not so smart after all.</text11>
			<text12>Wow, I'm impressed. Here's your gift...</text12>
			<text13>This mirror can take you to the realms of the major gods.</text13>
			<text14>I bet Athena didn't give you anything as awesome as that!</text14>
			<text15>Hello.</text15>
			<text16>Are you the mortal who my smarty-pants sister Athena is helping?</text16>
			<text17>Yup. That's me.</text17>
			<text18>Hmph. Well, I can help mortals too.</text18>
			<text19>I can use all the help I can get.</text19>
			<text20>Since Athena thinks you're so smart, pass this test and I will give you a useful gift.</text20>
		</poseidonBeach>
		
		<poseidonThrone>
			<text1>You must be Poseidon.</text1>
			<text2>I know why you have come. My brother Zeus is mad with power.</text2>
			<text3>I cannot leave the sea. But I will give you my trident.</text3>
			<text4>Thanks to you, our world is safe again.</text4>
		</poseidonThrone>
		
		<poseidonWater>
			<text1>I need air!!!</text1>
			<text2>Wow, thanks!</text2>
			<text3>I don't have the strength to break through this barrier.</text3>
			<text4>Looks like you could use a hand... or rather, a foot.</text4>
			<text5>No problem, kid. I'll wait here for you.</text5>
		</poseidonWater>
		
		<sphinx>
			<text1>What do I have to do?</text1>
			<text2>To gain one of my flowers, you must pass my test.</text2>
			<text3>What once was wet is now dried up.</text3>
			<text4>When once again the water flows</text4>
			<text5>then I will grant you one red rose.</text5>
			<text6>Your fate awaits you.</text6>
		</sphinx>
		
		<treeBottom>
			<text1>What do you mean?</text1>
			<text2>What about my immortality?</text2>
			<text3>Give them back!!!</text3>
			<text4>It says, "Whoever wields the five sacred objects will rule all of Poptropica!"</text4>
			<text5>What do I do?</text5>
			<text6>But he won't help!</text6>
			<text7>Things are not always what they seem to be.</text7>
			<text8>This is not good.</text8>
			<text9>Only the power of Poseidon and Hades can stop my father.</text9>
			<text10>Hercules can help you reach them.</text10>
			<text11>Ask him again. You must hurry!</text11>
			<text12>I am Athena. Be careful dealing with my father. He isn't honest.</text12>
			<text13>Can you help me?</text13>
			<text14>Look to the olive trees if you need my help.</text14>
			<text15>Thanks. Anything else I should know?</text15>
			<text16>My brother Hercules might help you, if you can convince him.</text16>
			<text17>I see you have the five objects.</text17>
			<text18>I have learned something about them. They are dangerous!</text18>
			<text19>Take a closer look at those clues...</text19>
			<text20>I wouldn't cross this bridge right now. The Sphinx is in a foul mood!</text20>
			<text21>Thank you! Now I can control all of Poptropica!</text21>
			<text22>Foolish mortal! I was just using you.</text22>
			<text23>Not a chance! By midnight all of Poptropica will be under my control!</text23>
			<text24>I dare you to pick an apple!</text24>
			<text25>Uh oh, you shouldn't have picked that apple!</text25>
			<text26>Did you complete your quest yet?</text26>
			<text27>I double dare you to pick an apple!</text27>
			<text28>We're just statues. Why would you listen to us?</text28>
			<text29>Welcome back.</text29>
		</treeBottom>
		
		<treeTop>
			<text1>Um, sorry. Do you want it back?</text1>
			<text2>What if I refuse?</text2>
			<text3>Okay, then. What do I have to do?</text3>
			<text4>Oops. Time's up!</text4>
			<text5>Can you help me get the golden apple?</text5>
			<text6>The nymphs hid all my honey! Collect 10 jars before time runs out and I'll help you.</text6>
			<text7>Well I think I'll be leaving now...</text7>
			<text8>Thanks for the honey. Use this secret path to reach the apple.</text8>
			<text9>Hurry and get my honey!</text9>
			<text10>Who has picked an apple of immortality?</text10>
			<text11>I will grant you immortality. But first, you must perform a task.</text11>
			<text12>Then all of Poptropica will feel my wrath!</text12>
		</treeTop>
		
		<shared>
			<text1>Find these five sacred items and return them here to me. When you have found them all, the gift of immortality will be yours.</text1>
			<text2>A flower from the Garden of the Sphinx.</text2>
			<text3>The golden ring of the Minotaur.</text3>
			<text4>A scale from the Hydra.</text4>
			<text5>A giant pearl from the kingdom of Poseidon.</text5>
			<text6>A whisker from Cerberus, the guardian of the Underworld.</text6>
			<text7>This mirror can take you to certain places in the realms of the gods, but only if you've already been there once.</text7>
			<text8>LOOK TO THE OLIVE TREES IF YOU NEED MY HELP.</text8>
			<text9>MUSIC CAN OPEN UP NEW DOORS.</text9>
			<text10>MUSIC SOOTHES THE SAVAGE BEAST.</text10>
			<text11>THE LABYRINTH IS A PUZZLING MAZE. USE THIS MAGIC THREAD TO FIND YOUR WAY.</text11>
			<text12>HEED THIS LESSON THAT MY UNCLES NEVER LEARNED: TWO POWERS COMBINED WILL DEFEAT THE POWER OF ONE.</text12>
			<text13>There's nothing to buy for one drachma here.</text13>
			<text14>The bag is out of wind.</text14>
			<text15>Hades said I'd know what to do when the time came.</text15>
			<text16>Poseidon said I'd know what to do when the time came.</text16>
			<text17>There's no reason to use this here.</text17>
			<text18>Doesn't seem to have any effect here.</text18>
			<text19>I really don't want to visit Aphrodite.</text19>
			<text20>Hey, I already helped you there.</text20>
			<text21>I already moved the boulder.</text21>
			<text22>I don't think you're ready to face Zeus yet, kid.</text22>
			<text23>The door won't open.</text23>
			<text24>Who are you?</text24>
			<text25>Can you stop him?</text25>
			<text26>Thanks! What do I do with it?</text26>
			<text27>You will know when the time comes.</text27>
			<text28>It looks like an offering altar.</text28>
			<text29>Where to next?</text29>
		</shared>
	</island>
</language>