<language>
	<island>
		<deepestOcean>
			<text1>You're too deep! You need to get back to the surface!</text1>
			<text2>Wait, what IS that? Keep the camera steady!</text2>
			<text3>How do I use this thing?</text3>
			<text4>I think we're going to need a bigger lens.</text4>
		</deepestOcean>
		
		<ledge>
			<text1>Be careful around that ledge! The sub isn't built for deeper water!</text1>
			<text2>Ahh!</text2>
		</ledge>
		
		<maze>
			<text1>The Angler Fish lives in a cave around here! It'll only show its face to eat.</text1>
			<text2>Watch out for the prickly urchins. They scare the fish!</text2>
			<text3>She's coming out. Roll film!</text3>
			<text4>Hold it steady...</text4>
			<text5>Almost got her, let's try more fish!</text5>
			<text6>Great filming. We got her!</text6>
			<text7>Anglers are shy, try finding some fish to lure her out!</text7>
		</maze>
		
		<reef>
			<text1>That's a Barreleye!  Find a way to flush it into the open.</text1>
			<text2>Looks like we can use the deep sea vents to scare it out of there, see if you can find more!</text2>
			<text3>We can't get a shot while it's behind these rocks. We'll need to move it into the open.</text3>
			<text4>The reef is blocking our shot, maybe we can move the fish to an opening.</text4>
			<text5>Look, there's a Stonefish hiding along the sea floor.</text5>
			<text6>Good idea, hiding behind the yellow coral will camouflage the sub!</text6>
			<text7>We can't get a shot while he's hiding, maybe if we weren't in the open he'd come out.</text7>
			<text8>He won't come out if he sees us, maybe we could find a place to hide.</text8>
			<text9>There's a rare purple Cuttlefish using camouflage to hide in the coral.</text9>
			<text10>Hmmm, the other Cuttlefish don't like to share their coral patches, see if you can use that to get the shot.</text10>
			<text11>Its colors blend with this coral patch. Maybe a different location would work better.</text11>
			<text12>Its camouflage works too well. We need to move it somewhere it's less effective.</text12>
			<text13>Look, a Hydromedusa! That's definitely a fish we should film. Don't let it get away!</text13>
		</reef>
		
		<ship>
			<text1>What's going on?</text1>
			<text2>Locked, I'll need the key to open this.</text2>
			<text3>I already got the ink.</text3>
			<text4>I can't use that here.</text4>
			<text5>I need to get closer to use that.</text5>
			<text6>I need help filming some underwater footage of these fish.</text6>
			<text7>Find the key to the sub and we'll make the greatest fish story ever told!</text7>
			<text8>Success! You take the sub and I'll keep in touch by radio.</text8>
			<text9>Get the key to that box and you can take the sub down. We'll make the greatest fish story ever!</text9>
			<text10>Great you have the key! Use it on the box.</text10>
			<text11>Ok, now get into the sub and start your undersea voyage!</text11>
			<text12>We can't let Cam back into the sub. It's for his own safety!</text12>
			<text13>Hey! Watch it!</text13>
			<text14>Well, it's just water... it won't stain.</text14>
			<text15>Where did that key go? I can't see a thing!</text15>
			<text16>Ack! My beautiful helmet!</text16>
			<text17>What are you doing in the middle of the ocean?</text17>
			<text18>We're on an expedition for Cam Jameson's fish film. Whether he'll finish it is another story.</text18>
			<text19>How long have you been out here?</text19>
			<text20>Weeks! Cam spends so much time in the sub that we had to lock it up for his own safety.</text20>
			<text21>Is that the key to the sub?</text21>
			<text22>Yes, but I can't let you have it. The safety of the crew is at stake.</text22>
			<text23>Cam loses all track of time when he's down there. He could wreck the equipment.</text23>
		</ship>
		
		<shipUnderside>
			<text1>We can't get a good shot when it hides behind the coral like that.</text1>
			<text2>There's a sea dragon. Track it down and click on it to record some footage!</text2>
			<text3>Good work, but the really good stuff is down a lot deeper!</text3>
			<text4>How do I use this thing?</text4>
		</shipUnderside>
		
		<shared>
			<text1>That fish is too far away, let's get closer.</text1>
			<text2>Great, now keep him in front of the camera to finish the shot.</text2>
			<text3>We can't get a good shot, we'll need another solution.</text3>
			<text4>Looks like we lost him.</text4>
			<text5>You got the shot. Nice work!</text5>
			<text6>We need a shot of the purple Cuttlefish, not the red one.</text6>
			<text7>We already have footage of that fish, keep looking.</text7>
			<text8>Go catch me some fish!</text8>
			<text9>That fish is too far away, I'll need to get closer.</text9>
		</shared>
	</island>
</language>