<language>
	<island>
		<aztec>
			<text1>Ssssssh! I'm spying!</text1>
			<text2>I am king of the Aztec Empire.</text2>
			<text3>A piece from the sun stone has disappeared!</text3>
			<text4>Find and return the missing piece!</text4>
			<text5>I have the sun stone piece!</text5>
			<text6>Thank you! We will remember you forever!</text6>
			<text7>Tell me about the sun stone.</text7>
			<text8>It is dedicated to the sun god Tonatiuh, who keeps us from catastrophe.</text8>
			<text9>You've restored the sun stone! What else could I need?</text9>
			<text10>I am queen of the Aztec Empire.</text10>
			<text11>The king is upset, because a piece from the sun stone has disappeared.</text11>
			<text12>Find out what happened to the sun stone!</text12>
			<text13>Thank you for restoring the sun stone!</text13>
			<text14>Did you see what happened to the sun stone? The gods must be very angry!</text14>
			<text15>Thank you! The gods are pleased!</text15>
			<text16>I can see you're not from around here. Watch out for the guards!</text16>
			<text17>The queen seems worried about something.</text17>
			<text18>Thank you for bringing peace to our queen.</text18>
			<text19>Welcome to our great city, traveler.</text19>
			<text20>I'm too old for this! You're young. Here, take my warrior mask.</text20>
			<text21>You'll make a good warrior with that mask.</text21>
			<text22>You can keep that weird mask I gave you.</text22>
			<text23>Hello, fellow warrior! Check out this cool mask I found!</text23>
			<text24>I like your mask.</text24>
		</aztec>
		
		<china>
			<text1>I'm supposed to send smoke signals to the other towers.</text1>
			<text2>You look concerned.</text2>
			<text3>I am! I can't find my stone bowl!</text3>
			<text4>What would you do with a stone bowl?</text4>
			<text5>I need it to make smoke signals. Without it I can't warn the others if there's danger!</text5>
			<text6>I have the stone bowl!</text6>
			<text7>Thank you! Now I'll be ready to send smoke signals when needed.</text7>
			<text8>Like the amulet I'm wearing? You can win it if you beat me in a simple memory game.</text8>
			<text9>You've already won the amulet, but you can play again if you'd like.</text9>
			<text10>Sorry, that's wrong. Try again sometime.</text10>
			<text11>Lucky guess! Here, take the amulet.</text11>
			<text12>Lucky guess!</text12>
			<text13>We mix sticky rice and lime together to make mortar for the wall.</text13>
			<text14>Be careful, this is a construction zone!</text14>
		</china>
		
		<desolation>
			<text1>I'm you, but 50 years older.</text1>
			<text2>What is this place?</text2>
			<text3>This will be your future if history is not restored!</text3>
			<text4>Can you help me repair the past?</text4>
			<text5>Take this time travel device. Now hurry, our future depends on you!</text5>
			<text6>Return to me when the past has been restored.</text6>
		</desolation>
		
		<edison>
			<text1>Welcome to Edison's workshop.</text1>
			<text2>If you're looking for Thomas Edison, he's inside.</text2>
			<text3>You like that motor wagon? It was shipped here from Germany!</text3>
		</edison>
		
		<edison2>
			<text1>I'm Thomas Edison. I'm an inventor.</text1>
			<text2>My phonograph is gone! It's an important invention and I need it back!</text2>
			<text3>Please let me know if you see my phonograph!</text3>
			<text4>I have your phonograph!</text4>
			<text5>I was so worried!</text5>
			<text6>Thank you for returning it.</text6>
			<text7>What is a phonograph, anyway?</text7>
			<text8>It's an invention of mine that records and plays sounds.</text8>
			<text9>I'm all set. Thanks for returning my phonograph!</text9>
			<text10>If you're looking for Edison, he's up one level.</text10>
			<text11>Welcome! Please be careful as you view our current experiments.</text11>
			<text12>Excuse me. I've got a lot of work to do.</text12>
		</edison2>
		
		<!-- <everest/> -->
		
		<everest2>
			<text1>I am Edmund Hillary.</text1>
			<text2>Tenzing and I are climbing to summit of Mount Everest.</text2>
			<text3>I've lost my climbing goggles! Let me know if you see them.</text3>
			<text4>I found your goggles!</text4>
			<text5>Thank you! Now we can continue climbing.</text5>
			<text6>Edmund has lost his climbing goggles.</text6>
		</everest2>
		
		<everest3>
			<text1>I can't believe I'm finally here at the peak of Everest! I couldn't have done it without your help.</text1>
			<text2>Wow! The view from here is amazing!</text2>
		</everest3>
		
		<france>
			<text1>I'm Alexandre Gustave Eiffel, the engineer for this project.</text1>
			<text2>We're building a great statue to give to the Americans.</text2>
			<text3>How is the construction going?</text3>
			<text4>We've got a big problem. The study model has disappeared!</text4>
			<text5>You have the model! Please bring it to Bartholdi.</text5>
			<text6>Now that the study model is back we can continue construction!</text6>
			<text7>There's something up on the ledge of the building.</text7>
			<text8>I see you managed to reach that book on the ledge.</text8>
			<text9>We don't have much to do. Work on the statue has been halted.</text9>
			<text10>Well, I'd better get back to work.</text10>
		</france>
		
		<france2>
			<text1>I am Frederic Auguste Bartholdi, sculptor of the statue.</text1>
			<text2>What is wrong?</text2>
			<text3>My original study model is gone! I must have it back!</text3>
			<text4>Please! You must find and return my sculpture!</text4>
			<text5>I have your study model!</text5>
			<text6>My study model! Thank you for returning it!</text6>
			<text7>Tell me about the study model.</text7>
			<text8>It's the original sculpture I made as a reference for the statue.</text8>
			<text9>Thank you for returning the model. You've saved this project!</text9>
			<text10>Bartholdi is distraught. His study model is missing.</text10>
			<text11>Break's over. Time to get back to work.</text11>
		</france2>
		
		<future>
			<text1>Hello [PlayerName]. You're looking youthful today! Heading back up to your sky home?</text1>
			<text2>Are you lost again? You'll have to ride the monorails and the hover platform to get back to your sky home.</text2>
			<text3>The monorail will be here any second.</text3>
			<text4>Going up?</text4>
		</future>
		
		<future2>
			<text1>Would you please stop following me around!</text1>
			<text2>Welcome home. I've been waiting for you.</text2>
			<text3>Take this gold medallion. You've earned it!</text3>
			<text4>I am you 50 years in the future.</text4>
			<text5>What do you like most about the future?</text5>
			<text6>We live our lives in a way that doesn't harm the earth.</text6>
			<text7>So the future has been saved?</text7>
			<text8>You've done your part. But people all around the world have a large part to play too.</text8>
		</future2>
		
		<graff>
			<text1>I'm Benjamin Franklin. I wonder what's taking Jefferson so long in there!</text1>
		</graff>
		
		<graff2>
			<text1>I am Thomas Jefferson!</text1>
			<text2>I just completed a draft of the Declaration of Independence, but it's disappeared!</text2>
			<text3>What can I do to help?</text3>
			<text4>I need that Declaration back! The future of this nation depends on it!</text4>
			<text5>I have the Declaration!</text5>
			<text6>Thank you! You've saved the future of this nation!</text6>
			<text7>I'm John Adams. We're in trouble, because Jefferson has lost the declaration!</text7>
			<text8>It's a good thing you came along!</text8>
		</graff2>
		
		<greece>
			<text1>Stay back! We can't trust anyone near the treasury any more!</text1>
			<text2>Thank you! As a reward, you may speak to the oracle on the hill.</text2>
			<text3>We're guarding the treasury. We don't want anything else stolen.</text3>
			<text4>Something was stolen?</text4>
			<text5>The prized golden vase is gone!</text5>
			<text6>Can I help?</text6>
			<text7>If you return the golden vase, you may talk to the oracle.</text7>
			<text8>I have the golden vase!</text8>
			<text9>Courage is the first of human qualities because it is the quality which guarantees the others.</text9>
			<text10>The oracle will only talk to those who donate to the treasury.</text10>
			<text11>Greetings, stranger. Welcome to Delphi.</text11>
		</greece>
		
		<greece2>
			<text1>I am the oracle of Delphi.</text1>
			<text2>If you wish to hear a prophecy, you must make a donation at the treasury.</text2>
			<text3>What should I donate?</text3>
			<text4>I see our golden vase inside a sealed cave that must be blown open. I see a barrel of explosive powder near a great stone wall.</text4>
			<text5>I prophesy. I can help you know what to do.</text5>
			<text6>Please help me!</text6>
			<text7>I see a group of sea voyagers who have lost an amulet.</text7>
			<text8>I see a man on a mud building who has lost a bag of salt rocks.</text8>
			<text9>I see an inventive artist who mourns the loss of his notebook.</text9>
			<text10>I see the king of a great empire standing near a broken sun stone.</text10>
			<text11>I see a guard on a great wall who needs a smoke signal bowl.</text11>
			<text12>I see a patriot who has lost an important document.</text12>
			<text13>I see a company of explorers who seek a silver medal.</text13>
			<text14>I see an inventor in a white building who has lost a prized invention.</text14>
			<text15>I see a sculptor who has lost his statue.</text15>
			<text16>I see a mountain climber who needs his climbing goggles.</text16>
			<text17>The future is sound, There is nothing more to be found.</text17>
			<text18>I see a great stone wall. I see a man wearing an amulet that does not belong to him.</text18>
			<text19>I see a red building near a field of cows. I see a bag of white rocks on top of this building.</text19>
			<text20>I see the construction of a great statue. I see a leather book on the ledge of a nearby building.</text20>
			<text21>I see a magical chariot with three wheels. I see a colorful piece of stone atop a white building.</text21>
			<text22>I see a company of explorers. I see a stone bowl at the top of a dead tree.</text22>
			<text23>I see a city made of mud. I see a man trading an important document.</text23>
			<text24>I see an artist's workshop. I see a silver medal hanging from a wooden platform.</text24>
			<text25>I see a strange device on top of our treasury.</text25>
			<text26>I see the peak of the tallest mountain. I see a small statue extending its arm.</text26>
			<text27>I see enormous temples. I see you wearing a feathered mask. I see a man wearing glass circles over his eyes.</text27>
			<text28>I see a beautiful future. I see you going to the top of the highest building.</text28>
		</greece2>
		
		<lab>
			<text1>That printout will explain everything. We're counting on you!</text1>
			<text2>Please help us! A malfunction has mixed up the past and now the future is in peril!</text2>
			<text3>This printout will explain everything. We're counting on you!</text3>
			<text4>It appears that you've repaired the past! Now travel to the future to make sure!</text4>
			<text5>Thank you! The future is looking bright!</text5>
			<text6>You will need to power up the Time Machine before you can use it.</text6>
			<text7>You did it! Time has been restored!</text7>
			<text8>What is this thing?</text8>
			<text9>This machine will transport you 50 years into the future.</text9>
			<text10>Why would I need to visit the future?</text10>
			<text11>So you can see the outcome of changes made in the past.</text11>
			<text12>How do I operate the machine?</text12>
			<text13>Power it up, then step inside.</text13>
		</lab>
		
		<lewis>
			<text1>I am Captain Meriwether Lewis!</text1>
			<text2>What are you doing out here?</text2>
			<text3>We're on an expedition to the west,but we've lost our Peace Medal!</text3>
			<text4>We dare not continue into Indian territory without a Peace Medal.</text4>
			<text5>I found the Peace Medal!</text5>
			<text6>Excellent! You must have keen eyes!</text6>
			<text7>No, Thank you! We'll offer this medal as a gift to the Nez Perce Indians.</text7>
			<text8>I am William Clark.</text8>
			<text9>We're exploring the Missouri river on its course to the west.</text9>
			<text10>Our Peace Medal has disappeared. We want to offer it as a gift to the Indians.</text10>
			<text11>You have the Peace Medal? Please take it to Lewis!</text11>
			<text12>I'm Toussaint Charbonneau, an interpreter and a cook.</text12>
			<text13>I'm Sacagawea, Charbonneau's wife and an interpreter for the expedition.</text13>
			<text14>I'm York, Clark's servant. Let him know if you see a silver medal lying around!</text14>
		</lewis>
		
		<mainStreet>
			<text1>Something's wrong over at Pendulum's Lab!</text1>
			<text2>Looks like things have calmed down at Pendulum's lab.</text2>
			<text3>Help! Something terrible has happened, and now the future is in peril!</text3>
			<text4>Please come in!</text4>
		</mainStreet>
		
		<mali>
			<text1>I'm just a poor trader.</text1>
			<text2>I came to Timbuktu to trade, but I can't find the salt rocks I brought!</text2>
			<text3>What would you do with salt rocks?</text3>
			<text4>Salt is valuable here. Losing that bag is a big loss for my family!</text4>
			<text5>Thank you! You've saved my family's fortune!</text5>
			<text6>I found your salt rocks!</text6>
			<text7>Thank you! I was afraid my fortune had been lost!</text7>
			<text8>You're not from around here, are you? Welcome to the Mali Empire!</text8>
			<text9>If you're looking for the document merchant, he's inside the inn.</text9>
		</mali>
		
		<mali2>
			<text1>You have the document you wanted, but you can piece the painting together again if you'd like.</text1>
			<text2>Greetings. Would you like to see the documents I'm currently trading?</text2>
			<text3>You're getting good at that!</text3>
			<text4>A promise is a promise. The document is yours.</text4>
			<text5>My pet snakes are on the loose outside. Watch out!</text5>
			<text6>Hello stranger. Welcome to Timbuktu.</text6>
		</mali2>
		
		<docsPopup>
			<text1>You seem most interested in this foreign document.</text1>
	    	<text2>But I see you have no money...</text2>
	    	<text3>However, if you can help me I will give you the document you seek.</text3>
	    	<text4>Can you piece this painting together for me?</text4>
	    	<text5>It's a portrait of the great king Mansa Musa!</text5>
	    	<text6>This is wonderful!</text6>
		</docsPopup>
		
		<renaissance>
			<text1>Welcome to the Clos Luce mansion.</text1>
			<text2>That was an impressive jump!</text2>
			<text3>There's a strange object hanging from the bottom of the deck!</text3>
		</renaissance>
		
		<renaissance2>
			<text1>I am Leonardo Da Vinci.</text1>
			<text2>What do you do here?</text2>
			<text3>I'm an artist and an inventor, but I've lost something important to me!</text3>
			<text4>What did you lose?</text4>
			<text5>My notebook. It contains valuable information. I must have it back!</text5>
			<text6>I'm an artist and an inventor.</text6>
			<text7>This notebook is all I needed. Thank you!</text7>
			<text8>I found your notebook!</text8>
			<text9>Thank you! As a reward you may take this prototype of my latest invention.</text9>
			<text10>You must be looking for Da Vinci. He's up on the top floor.</text10>
		</renaissance2>
		
		<viking>
			<text1>I'll need something to blast through these rocks.</text1>
			<text2>We're on a voyage of exploration. We landed here to wait out the storm.</text2>
			<text3>We've lost an important item. Without it, we dare not face the sea.</text3>
			<text4>What did you lose?</text4>
			<text5>Thor's Hammer, an amulet with protective powers.</text5>
			<text6>Tell me about the amulet.</text6>
			<text7>It's called Thor's Hammer. It protects us while at sea.</text7>
			<text8>Thank you for your help. We'll set sail first thing in the morning.</text8>
			<text9>I have your amulet!</text9>
			<text10>Thank you! The powers of Thor are with us again!</text10>
			<text11>I'm tired and wet. I want to get off this island!</text11>
			<text12>I'm so glad you found the amulet!</text12>
			<text13>If we don't find that amulet, we'll be stuck here forever!</text13>
			<text14>Thanks for your help! I can't wait to set sail in the morning!</text14>
		</viking>
		
		<viking2>
			<text1>Torches don't work in water. I'll need to be more careful!</text1>
			<text2>The torch burned out. I'll have to move faster!</text2>
		</viking2>
		
		<shared>
			<text1>Who are you?</text1>
			<text2>Is there anything else you need?</text2>
			<text3>Ouch! That's hot!</text3>
			<text4>What do you do?</text4>
			<text5>What are you doing?</text5>
			<text6>What are you doing up here?</text6>
			<text7>Why are you stopped here?</text7>
			<text8>Is something wrong?</text8>
			<text9>How can I help?</text9>
		</shared>
	</island>
</language>