<language>
	<island>
		<computer>
			<text78>You fool! Watch where you're going!</text78>
			<text79>What are you doing!? You'll destroy my Rabbot!</text79>
			<text80>You'll pay for this!!!</text80>
			<text40>Aaaaaaaah!!!!</text40>
		</computer>
		
		<diner>
			<text59>I'm Tony, the owner of this diner.</text59>
			<text60>How's business?</text60>
			<text61>Mamma Mia! It's never been worse!</text61>
			<text62>Who are those people on the bulletin?</text62>
			<text63>Those people have all been missing for several months!</text63>
			<text64>Grazie tanto! Thank you for bringing back business!</text64>
			<text65>Of course. You think I hang out here for fun?</text65>
			<text66>Honey, I'm just happy to have a job!</text66>
			<text67>What's that in your hand?</text67>
			<text68>It's a pitcher of milk.</text68>
			<text69>Do you work here?</text69>
			<text70>I sure do!</text70>
			<text71>How's work?</text71>
			<text72>Things are going much better now!</text72>
			<text73>Thanks for the milk.</text73>
			<text74>No problem, honey.</text74>
			<text75>Can you fill this bowl with milk?</text75>
			<text76>Sure!</text76>
			<text77>I wouldn't be here if it weren't for you!</text77>
		</diner>
		
		<factory>
			<text58>I can't pry this open with my bare hands!</text58>
		</factory>
		
		<farm>
			<text55>This used to be the greatest carrot farm in the world. But the carrots all disappeared, and now we're left with nothing.</text55>
			<text56>Now that the carrots aren't disappearing, I can make this into a great farm once again!</text56>
			<text57>Home, sweet home! I've got a lot of work to do now!</text57>
		</farm>
		
		<farmHouse>
			<text51>I don't think he's coming down without good reason.</text51>
			<text52>I think he liked the milk.</text52>
			<text53>Meow</text53>
			<text54>Purr</text54>
		</farmHouse>
		
		<loading>
			<text46>Can't talk. Must load carrots.</text46>
			<text47>Hey, what's that behind you!?</text47>
			<text48>You are not authorized to use this printer.</text48>
			<text49>Thank you for freeing me! Follow me, there's something you should see.</text49>
			<text50>Thanks again! Now watch out! If you're seen without rabbot ears you'll be captured!</text50>
		</loading>
		
		<mainStreet>
			<text1>What's wrong?</text1>
			<text2>Our beloved town is in ruins!</text2>
			<text3>What happened?</text3>
			<text4>All of our carrots have vanished! Our economy is falling apart!</text4>
			<text5>What can I do to help?</text5>
			<text6>Find out what's happened to our carrots!</text6>
			<text7>The carrots have stopped disappearing!</text7>
			<text8>You've saved our town! As mayor, I present you with this medallion!</text8>
			<text9>Thank you! Now we can get started on making this town great again!</text9>
			<text10>I haven't been able to find work since the factory closed down.</text10>
			<text11>There's lots of work to be done!</text11>
			<text12>Sorry, but we're plumb out of gas.</text12>
			<text13>Things are looking up around here.</text13>
			<text14>I should be able to reopen the station soon!</text14>
			<text15>It's good to be back home! Thanks!</text15>
		</mainStreet>
		
		<processing>
			<text37>Can't talk. Must process carrots.</text37>
			<text38>Look out behind you!</text38>
			<text39>Thank you! Now be careful. If you're seen without rabbot ears Dr. Hare will catch you!</text39>
			<text44>Look! A flying buffalo!</text44>
			<text45>I'm free! You should probably find some rabbot ears, or Dr. Hare will find you!</text45>
		</processing>
		
		<robot>
			<text30>Why are you standing around!? Get to the computer and start the launch sequence!</text30>
			<text31>I'll be waiting in the cockpit. Now move it!</text31>
			<text32>Can't talk. Must initiate launch sequence.</text32>
			<text33>Look, a giant bunny!</text33>
			<text34>You are not authorized to use this computer.</text34>
			<text35>Dr. Hare is going to use his giant rabbot to mind control the entire planet from space!</text35>
			<text36>You did it! Now let's get out of here.</text36>
		</robot>
		
		<surplus>
			<text16>I found your cat!</text16>
			<text17>I'm Charlie.</text17>
			<text18>Feeling down?</text18>
			<text19>I lost my cat, Whiskers. If you can find her, I'll give you a crowbar for free!</text19>
			<text20>Where did you last see your cat?</text20>
			<text21>Well, she used to hang out by the old farm house.</text21>
			<text22>Is there anything else you need?</text22>
			<text23>I'm okay, but this town sure could use some help!</text23>
			<text24>Whiskers looks happy to be home.</text24>
			<text25>Yes, thank you so much for finding him!</text25>
			<text26>Nope. You've helped me and the whole town already!</text26>
			<text27>Whiskers!!! Come here, you little rascal!</text27>
			<text28>Thank you! I can't afford to give you much, but maybe you could use this crowbar.</text28>
			<text29>I'm enjoying my freedom. Thanks!</text29>
		</surplus>
		
		<shared>
			<text41>Who are you?</text41>
			<text42>What are you doing?</text42>
			<text43>Where?</text43>
		</shared>
	</island>
</language>